So I read in the Daily News that Tish James said that my case is not deed theft and she had been
working closely with the family for the last two years. Tish James did not work with me for the
last two years. Any type of attention from your office with the NYPD, make sure that while we're
all figuring out all of these facts and case-by-case faces that these folks are not being
involved. And so I want the list and I believe the list she's going to provide to us. I'm
going to call the chief judge and let him know that we should issue a moratorium or stay on
all these evictions. Have there allegations of deed theft, mortgage foreclosure or some
criminality that need to be investigated as soon as possible.
I'm with the Judge Street Journal. I just had a quick question about your office saying that
the home that was arrested outside wasn't actually the victim of deed theft. Can you comment on that?
It technically wasn't a deed theft. It emanated from deed theft. It originated from deed theft,
but it was an eviction proceeding. And we had been involved in that case for some time. We
analyzed it. But at the end of the day, I'm glad that the council member focused on bringing to light
the problem of deed theft, an issue that I've been focusing on for a very long time. Thank you.
This law, see, I wrote it here. This law right here is 756A. You see it's from the AG's office.
This law means if you say there's a title discrepancy, they're supposed to investigate it.
Every six months, there's supposed to be a brief from whatever agency picks it up to give some type
of feedback about the case. So if my case, because she did say in the Daily News that my case was
um, this was not a deed theft case, well, they never, no agency even looked at the case to say
exactly what it was. And we are ensuring that city government is doing its part to protect
vulnerable homeowners. The Office of Deed Theft Provincial will coordinate closely with HPD and our
city's Commission on Human Rights. So I really want to acknowledge this mayor for for taking a step
and putting money where his mouth is and opening this office. We can no longer show up for press
conferences and say that we now have an office of deed theft and less than 72 hours later,
we have police, marshal, whoever else, the federal government. We don't know who these people are
that are coming here. So what was that? Was it a photo app? Was it a thing to say that we did something?
Or are we serious about combating deed theft? I mean, you're a lawyer. And I know, I guess,
because you feel like you can just tell anybody anything, right? Because you're Letitia James,
you know, and they'll believe you. But I'm here to tell you, listen, that is not true. They didn't
do their job. And that's why. And the heat is on her because everybody's questioning her and saying,
hey, this is happening in your community and why you didn't do anything. And I'm here to tell y'all
she didn't do anything. We met with her. We have footage. We can show you. We don't have anything to hide.
She didn't support us. And she didn't help us. And I really think the reason why they don't help us,
I'm gonna be honest with you, because a lot of these lobbyists, the people that fund them,
are the people that's doing this to us. We need someone that's not compromised.
The United States has an unbreakable bond with Israel. Israel is a true friend. It is our
greatest ally in the region. It's great to be here at the annual conference in support of the
U.S.-Israel relationship.